import type { MCQ } from '../../../types'

export const mcqSet2: MCQ[] = [
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "The C-preprocessors are specified with _________symbol.",
    "options": [
      "#",
      "$",
      "\"\"",
      "&"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What is the output of this C code? int main() { int i = 7; i = i / 4; printf(\"%d\\n\", i); return 0; }",
    "options": [
      "Run time error",
      "1",
      "3",
      "Compile time error"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "What is the output of this C code? int main() { int i = -5; int k = i %4; printf(\"%d\\n\", k); }",
    "options": [
      "-1",
      "1",
      "-2",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "The standard header _______ is used for variable list arguments (...) in C.",
    "options": [
      "<starg.h>",
      "<stdrg.h>",
      "<stdar.h>",
      "<stdarg.h>"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "Operator % in C Language is called.?",
    "options": [
      "Percentage Operator",
      "Quotient Operator",
      "Modulus",
      "Division"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What is an expression?",
    "options": [
      "A statement that performs a specific task",
      "A combination of variables",
      "A data type used to store text",
      "A reserved keyword in programming languages"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What is the result of the expression 10 / 2 + 3 * 2?",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "13",
      "11",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "Which operator is used for string concatenation in many programming languages?",
    "options": [
      "+",
      "*",
      "/",
      "-"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "What is the purpose of parentheses in expressions?",
    "options": [
      "To denote comments",
      "To override operator precedence",
      "To indicate the end of a statement",
      "To multiply two values"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "Standard ANSI C recognizes ______ number of keywords?",
    "options": [
      "30",
      "32",
      "24",
      "36"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  }
]
